– Sure. So, hi. My name is Phil
Fairheller. I am the CTO and co-founder of
HealthKERI. And today I will be presenting
on KERI infrastructure, focusing mainly on
the components that HealthKERI just
donated to open source to the KERI
Foundation, that being the wallet
witnesses and watchers. Sure. So, if our
work in HealthKERI disappeared tomorrow,
the decentralized identity system would
lose its foothold in healthcare. Right
now, we are making a big difference in
bringing this technology into healthcare
to help secure data exchange between
providers, payers, and patients. And we
would miss out on that opportunity. So,
what we at HealthKERI see differently is
the impact that this technology can have
to facilitate rapid connections that are
needed to make healthcare move more
smoothly. Thank you.